Contact

sellis2528@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/susanellis-msn-sphr-shrm-scpfache-6502b329 (LinkedIn) arh.org (Company)

Top Skills

Employee Benefits

Deferred Compensation

Benefits Administration

Certifications

SPHR

Fellow of the American College of Healthcare Executives (FACHE) SHRM-SPC

Susan Ellis MSN, SPHR, SHRM-SCP, FACHE

Community CNO

Prestonsburg, Kentucky

Summary

Experienced Vice President with a demonstrated history of working in the hospital & health care industry. Skilled in Employee Handbooks, Deferred Compensation, Employee Benefits Design, Strategic Planning, and Organizational Development. Strong healthcare services professional with a MSN focused in Nursing from University of Kentucky.

Experience

Highlands ARH Regional Medical Center Community CNO February 1984 - Present (36 years 6 months)

Highlands Regional Medical Center Vice President Patient Care February 2013 - Present (7 years 6 months)

Highlands Health System
Vice President of Human Resources
May 2002 - Present (18 years 3 months)

Highlands Regional Medical Center Director of Educational Services January 1991 - May 2002 (11 years 5 months)

Education

University of Kentucky MSN, Nursng · (1991 - 1994)

Marshall University

Bachelor of Science, Nursing · (1987 - 1990)